<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Golang on Andrew Rady</title>
    <link>/tags/golang/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Golang on Andrew Rady</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 09:00:50 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/golang/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Mux Cors</title>
      <link>/posts/mux-cors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 09:00:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/mux-cors/</guid>
      <description>Handling CORS with Gorilla Mux In an earlier post I talked about create an API with golang using a few packages. One of the main ones packages many people use is mux for routes. This makes it easier handles routes within our application. Now we need setup our application to allow certain sites to talk with our api. Luckily Gorilla has another package that integrates seamlessly with Mux.
Setting up our routes Let&amp;rsquo;s make a function in our main.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go Api</title>
      <link>/posts/go-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 17:57:45 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/go-api/</guid>
      <description>Golang First API I have been following Golang for a little but. It seemed interesting to me for a few reasons. One major one was the speed of it. Another was it&amp;rsquo;s syntax is similar to python. I am no python developer, but I have made a few side project with it. SO I decided to update and an aging Rails application. It&amp;rsquo;s just a simple crud application that displays martial arts rings at tournaments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 22:37:00 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/first-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World! My name is Andrew Rady and I am currently a front end developer at Ritter Insurance Marketing working with Vue. I have been writing some blog post on our company blog at rimdev.io, but I wanted to start a personal one. On rimdev.io most of my articles are around vue since that is what I work on mostly, but I want to be able to share some of my experiences from side projects.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>